MURDER
ENCYLOPEDIA
I’m messed up in the head.
No one at this junior high realizes...
How the peaceful equilibrium of daily life...
You whacked off with a toilet paper roll?!
teeters on the edge...
Dude, I can’t believe it!
Try it out, man.
Maybe I’ll give it a go, eh?
Wonder if it’ll fit?
But man, what I’d give for a titjob!
Case File No. 8 T-Prefecture N-City “N City Council-
The truth behind the mid-day jump
that fooled everyone watching
No! Stop thinking about it!
I’m a bloodthirsty beast.
When will the day come?
When will I overcome these urges?
There’s the girl I want to kill most of all.
Anna Yamada.
The prettiest girl in school,
and a magazine model, apparently.
But I don’t give a damn.
All I want is to see that beautiful face writhing with pain.
I can hardly control myself.
That goddamn bitch!
I’ll make you regret ever looking down on me like that!
You know what?
I bet she’ll look just as beautiful as a corpse.
Her body will belong to her killer.
Yes, it will be all mine.
Every night I think the same thing,
and hate myself for it.
I’m really messed up in the head.
The classroom gets especially loud
and unbearable during lunch.
But this place, it’s much quieter.
Library
It’s the one place I feel at ease-
What?
What the heck?
What is she saying?!
Uhh...
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Thank goodness.
For what?
What did she say?
What the heck is she even doing here in the first place?!
Wait, hang on now. Is this my chance to kill her?
No, now’s not the time.
Potato Chips
Consomme Home Run
I should observe her.
What?
We just had lunch!
Potato Chips
Consomme Home Run
Isn’t that a party-sized bag?!
Why’s she smiling like that all alone?!
Wait, and what was with that rice ball?
Her humming is getting more and more ape-like!
What the hell?
What’s with this girl?!
Chill out, man.
Just think about how you’ll off her.
Human Anatomy
Diagrams
Is she working on the presentation
we have for Social Studies?
All right!
She’s not even gonna use a pencil, first?!
See? You ran out of space.
-Nations
Don’t pretend like it’s no big deal!
Huh? Where’s my box cutter?
I’ve got mine!
But wait a minute...
Here, you can use mine.
Why were you carrying it around with you?
What a creep...
If she pulls that,
then it’ll be time for my big murder spectacular.
Y-you can use this if you want...
You just cut my workload in half!
Oh, that wasn’t an intentional pun, okay?
Huh?
And, thanks!
At least she wasn’t creeped out?
Wait, forget that...
Yamada is using my box cutter...?!
My box cutter!
That’s mine!
Yamada, where have you been?
I bet you were sneaking in snacks all alone.
No, I wasn’t.
Here!
She’s giving me her leftovers?
Oh...
I wasn’t finished yet!
Hey! Don’t make other people do your dirty work!
I wasn’t!
Just when I was starting my murder countdown!
It’s been a full day since then.
My box cutter is still in her pencil case.
My sharp tool is in her...
Right. Figures.
It’s still warm!
Don’t tell me...!
Did she have it in her hand the whole way here?!
So she wouldn’t forget?
Hey, did you watch last night?
No, maybe she’s just trying not to
give me any chance to finish her off.
I did. Did you, Yamada?
Nope.
You didn’t?
Wait...
Seriously?
She knows which desk is mine, though?
Year 2 Class 3
Okay, today you’ll be giving your group presentations.
Huh?
This isn’t the poster I made yesterday.
Oh, that?
It was a mess, so I redid the whole thing!
What?! You bitch! How could you?!
She worked so hard on that!
Party System Comparison
Two-party System Nations
You did this one.
She worked so hard on that!
Didn’t really have much time, see?
Girls disgust me!
They can’t even hide how horrendously envious
they get of anyone prettier than them!
I mean, look.
Party System Comparison
Two-party System Nations
I could hardly believe you tried to use
this chocolate smudge as part of the title.
That is pretty terrible, I guess.
See?
Chocolate? Seriously?
You’re always so sloppy like that.
Doesn’t really look like she cares, though?
Party System Comparison
Two-party System Nations
We researched political party systems.
We looked up the US’ two party system
This is so boring...
and Japan’s political system you all know-
She’s got no life left in her!
That bit earlier must have hurt her feelings!
So basically...
I think we should adopt the two party system, too!
Shut your face!
SDGs Overview
Our group researched the SDGs.
I wrote out our poster, so I’ll let them handle the rest.
Are you all familiar with the SDGs?
SDG stands for Sustainable Development Goals,
Yamada?
and they got their start in 2000 at the United Nations as the MDGs,
Millennium Development Goals-
This dumb thing bothered her that much?!
Maybe in her eyes,
it meant a whole lot more.
There are 169 different targets-
Huh? Is that a helicopter?
Think something happened?
Look at ‘em all.
Think there was an accident?
Stop it!
Quit looking towards Yamada
while she’s crying you ass-hats!
I need to distract them!
That concludes our presentation.
What the heck are you doing?!
We’re finished, so who cares?
Go on, then.
I’m messed up in the head, anyway.
Now she can cry all she wants.
Isn’t that a weird looking helicopter?
Think it’s one of those osprey ones?
Like I know.
What the heck?!
Did you check out this month’s volume of CiEL?
Not yet.
We definitely oughta switch places here, you giant!
You’re so heavy!
Want an ass-kicking?!
Fine, then.
What is this, a moe anime?
They say girls who like that kinda
close-contact got sex on the mind, right?
Imagine Kobayashi is her boyfriend for a sec.
Freakin’ hot, right?
Quit being such a genius of a creep!
Wish a girl like Yamada and me could be FWBs.
I’m going to murder you, you pig!
I’m not really into girls that pretty.
This guy’s into ugly girls?
Who’s your type in this class, then?
S-someone like Hara, maybe?
You’re a real perv, dude.
Is your brain in your dick?
What the hell?
There she is again...
Hara!
Here for a book?
No, someone asked me to meet them here.
Want some?
No, I’m on a diet.
Me too...
Liar!
I eat what I want, when I want.
That’s my lifestyle!
Talk about saying something stupid like it’s smart!
Me too, but I wound up like this.
Don’t leave her hanging, say something!
Kanzaki?
Oh, you’re here already?
Yeah. So...
What did you want?
You’re kidding me!
Is he about to ask her out?!
Well, you see...
Yeah...?
Kinda strange seeing you two together, huh?
You’re screwing this up, Yamada.
Oh, hey! They say fiber’s good if you’re on a diet.
Right...
You’re on a diet?
I’m trying to lose weight.
I think girls are better with a little extra weight.
Guys have a totally different concept
of “little” there, you know.
Yeah.
No, but...
I like ‘em fat as they come.
100 kilos or more, see?
All squishy and layered.
Oookay.
Cut it out!
Quit telling Yamada about your pervy fetish!
Pretty rude of you to only figure this out NOW!
But you know what you gotta do now, right?
Go on, then.
Get outta there and leave them alone.
Is someone else in here?
M-maybe it was a cat?
No one’s gonna believe that!
A cat?
Is she trying to tell me to act like a cat?!
I wish I was dead.
I’ll go take a look.
A realistic meow isn’t gonna cut it...
That’s what they sound like when they fight.
Really?
Yeah.
That was a different cat, too.
They might get into a fight.
You’re into cats?
I have two of my own.
Wow, really?
Job’s done.
Like you did a damn thing...
Glad that worked, huh?
Yeah...
See ya.
What am I doing helping her out?!
Anna Yamada...
What’s that girl’s deal?
Why are we always crossing paths?
Books
Pay With Points
She said she was in this month’s volume, didn’t she?
Definitely can’t go in there dressed like this.
Thank you for shopping with us!
She said it was in CiEL, right?
Worry-free Fall Outfit Guide
New Fall Item Special
Knitted Garments for
Guaranteed Romance
This must be it.
Y-Yamada?!
No, it can’t be...
Oh, good, they have it!
I’ve been hooked on this magazine, lately.
Yeah? What’s in it?
Doesn’t this look so pretty?
Oh yeah, for sure!
Yup, that’s definitely her.
Is she seriously hoping to get noticed?
Don’t make eye-contact!
Way to lose the readers you needed.
Worry-free Fall Outfit Guide
New Fall Item Special
Knitted Garments for
Guaranteed Romance
What? Cut that out!
You’re messing with the whole store, now!
Quit standing ready to give out signatures,
you’re not even an author!
See? Right back where it should be.
She’s got a pretty cringeworthy side to her too, huh?
F-fine, guess I’ll just have to buy it to
make up for the girls she scared off.
REAL Horror Stories
Horrors coming for you, hidden in plain sight
Records of the Supernatural!
Bone-chilling Ghost Stories
Worry-free Fall Outfit Guide
New Fall Item Special
Knitted Garments for
Guaranteed Romance
Let’s see, then...
This might as well be from another planet...
Huh, I’m not seeing her in here...
There she is!
She looks like a complete stranger.
I don’t even give a damn, anymore.
What was I even so worked up about, anyway?
I mean...
Admission Ticket
Examinee No.
Name          Kyotaro Ichikawa
Examination Date         February 3rd
Me and Yamada have always been worlds apart.
List of Passing Examinees
What was I even thinking?
I don’t give a damn about anything, anymore.
Would be a waste not to use it
at least once I guess, though.
Hardly got a wink of sleep last night.
Why the hell did I have to buy that crap?
Is that... her boyfriend?!
I mean, it figures.
Of course she has one.
Yup. That’s just the way the world works.
Like I even care.
“LINE”? What’s that?
C’mon, I know you use it.
Like this, see?
I’m Haruya Nanjo.
Is he trying to pick her up?
What about social media?
“Soul shall me dia”?
You can’t play THAT dumb.
How do you keep in touch with your friends, then?
We can read each others minds by tuning
our brains to the same wavelength.
Oh, trying to weird him out, now?
The key is to tune your brain waves
to the electromagnetic waves-
Can you read what’s on my mind right now, then?
This guy’s determined!
You want some ice cream!
More like YOU do!
Nope!
I was actually thinking how
much cuter you look up close!
What a creep! She’s not into you, dude.
You’re pretty funny, you know that?
I am?! How so?!
THAT’S what she was waiting for?
That whole, “I don’t know what LINE is” bit.
I’ve used that one so many times,
I’ve got it down to a science!
I really don’t know what it is, though!
You really are funny.
Oh, come on.
Quit looking like you enjoy it...
Hey.
Really though, add me on LINE.
No, I-
Seriously, though.
I-
Fine...
Not like it matters.
Who cares?
I don’t, right?
Am I really messed up in the head?
Yamada!
Chii, did you see that?
Ichikawa just sent his bike flying.
She saw that?
What did you do that for?
No, I uhh...
Well...
I hit the gas instead of the brakes.
You’re pretty funny, Ichikawa.
I Was
I Was Stolen Away